<div>

  <h3>Abstract submission to 
47th Congress of the European Society of Paediatric Radiology</h3>

<p><font size="2" face="Arial">Welcome to the MyReview web-based conference 
management system! This website is devoted to abstract submissions for 
the <b>47</b><sup><b>th</b></sup><b> Congress of the European Society 
Paediatric Radiology</b>: this meeting will be held in Bordeaux, France, 
from 7th to 11th, June 2010.</font></p>

<p><font size="2" face="Arial">As an author, you can submit an abstract 
for a paper that you intend to present, using the abstract submission 
interface.</font></p>
<p><font color="#E36C0A" size="3" face="Arial">Instructions</font></p>
<p><font size="2" face="Arial">Dear colleague, please read first carefully, 
and eventually print, these lines. </font></p>
<p><font size="2" face="Arial"><b>1)</b> <b>Create an account</b>: See 
the guidelines. Please enter the information in the specific form to 
create your account. Note that all the fields are mandatory. You must 
provide a secure password. Your Email will be used to log in the system. 
Please note that MyReview always stores and compares email addresses 
in lowercase. If you have already created an account, or if your Email 
has been previously be entered in the database as co author of another 
paper, you will not be allowed to create another account and an error 
message will appeared: “This email is already used”; In this case, 
go to the login page, and follow the link “password forgotten”.</font></p>
<p><font size="2" face="Arial"><b>2)</b> <b>New submission:</b> Please 
use the form for your submission. </font></p>

<p><font size="2" face="Arial"><b>Title and 
Abstract:</b> Note that all the fields marked by a &#39;*&#39; are mandatory. 
The maximum size is 220 words, excluding title. Choose the main topic 
(one) of your proposition.</font></p>
<p><font size="2" face="Arial"><b>List of authors:</b> Enter the list 
of authors. Important: (i) you must appear in this list (use the &quot;Add 
me&quot; button to do so), (ii) all the fields are mandatory and (iii) 
there must be exactly one contact author (s/he will receive the confirmation 
mail). You can add more than 4 authors.</font></p>
<p><font size="2" face="Arial"><b>Additional questions:</b> you have 
to answer to all, with only one button. <br>

In case of conflict of interest, please give more information in the 
specific field at the end of the abstract form. <br>
You can submit a poster or oral presentation, accept or not that this 
last one could be changed into a poster after blind review by the scientific 
committee.  <br>
For your society of reattachment, only one answer. If you are member 
of several societies, choose the one in relation with your geographic 
origin.</font></p>
<p><font size="2" face="Arial"><b>3) Author console:</b> Your submission 
can then be accessed in the Author console, checked and modified until 
the submission deadline.</font></p>
<p><font size="2" face="Arial"><b>4) Abstract submission</b> is opened 
from 1<sup>st</sup> December, 2009. 
The deadline is 15t<sup>h</sup> 

January, 2010.</font></p>
<p><font color="#E36C0A" size="3" face="Arial">About Myreview</font></p>
<p><font size="2" face="Arial">MyReview is distributed under the Gnu 
Public Library (GPL) Licence and has been used by hundreds of conferences. 
Version 2 is a complete revision and brings several important features, 
including multi-languages support. © Philippe Rigaux, 2003-2009.</font></p>


</div>

</div>